{
	"dlm-1-en": {
		"id": "dlm-1-en",
		"prompt": "At karaoke, you sing",
		"left": "Almost like Mariah Carey",
		"right": "Just... really bad"
	},
	"dlm-2-en": {
		"id": "dlm-2-en",
		"prompt": "Propose in front of",
		"left": "Your in-laws",
		"right": "A cramped stadium, on the big screen"
	},
	"dlm-3-en": {
		"id": "dlm-3-en",
		"prompt": "Last-minute gift",
		"left": "Rewrapped Christmas present",
		"right": "Flowers picked at the park"
	},
	"dlm-4-en": {
		"id": "dlm-4-en",
		"prompt": "Reuse",
		"left": "Condom",
		"right": "Toilet paper",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-5-en": {
		"id": "dlm-5-en",
		"prompt": "President",
		"left": "Rihanna",
		"right": "Greta Thunberg"
	},
	"dlm-6-en": {
		"id": "dlm-6-en",
		"prompt": "Live in the world of",
		"left": "Star Wars, as a Jedi",
		"right": "X-men, as a mutant"
	},
	"dlm-7-en": {
		"id": "dlm-7-en",
		"prompt": "Befriend",
		"left": "An alien",
		"right": "A robot"
	},
	"dlm-8-en": {
		"id": "dlm-8-en",
		"prompt": "Amazing orgasm every time",
		"left": "For you",
		"right": "For your partners",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-9-en": {
		"id": "dlm-9-en",
		"prompt": "Midlife crisis",
		"left": "You get in debt for unnecessary stuff",
		"right": "You leave everything to raise goats in a village"
	},
	"dlm-10-en": {
		"id": "dlm-10-en",
		"prompt": "Super combo",
		"left": "Coke and coke",
		"right": "Acid and watermelon",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-11-en": {
		"id": "dlm-11-en",
		"prompt": "Drive like",
		"left": "Granny on a Sunday morning",
		"right": "Schumacher in a hurry"
	},
	"dlm-12-en": {
		"id": "dlm-12-en",
		"prompt": "Ideal home",
		"left": "Big living room",
		"right": "Big kitchen"
	},
	"dlm-13-en": {
		"id": "dlm-13-en",
		"prompt": "Spa",
		"left": "In a bathing suit",
		"right": "Naked",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-14-en": {
		"id": "dlm-14-en",
		"prompt": "Sponge bath from",
		"left": "Your father",
		"right": "The Pope",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-15-en": {
		"id": "dlm-15-en",
		"prompt": "Your plate at the end of a meal",
		"left": "Spotless, and your stomach hurts",
		"right": "There are still 2 spoonfuls left"
	},
	"dlm-16-en": {
		"id": "dlm-16-en",
		"prompt": "Your laugh",
		"left": "Seal",
		"right": "Pig"
	},
	"dlm-17-en": {
		"id": "dlm-17-en",
		"prompt": "Sitting next to you on a plane",
		"left": "The Joker",
		"right": "Hannibal Lecter"
	},
	"dlm-18-en": {
		"id": "dlm-18-en",
		"prompt": "Boost your confidence",
		"left": "2-3 shots",
		"right": "Soundtrack from Rocky"
	},
	"dlm-19-en": {
		"id": "dlm-19-en",
		"prompt": "Plastic surgery",
		"left": "You gotta do what you gotta do!",
		"right": "Over my dead body!"
	},
	"dlm-20-en": {
		"id": "dlm-20-en",
		"prompt": "Lose",
		"left": "All your teeth",
		"right": "One day of your life each time you kiss someone"
	},
	"dlm-21-en": {
		"id": "dlm-21-en",
		"prompt": "In a plane",
		"left": "You sleep",
		"right": "You pray"
	},
	"dlm-22-en": {
		"id": "dlm-22-en",
		"prompt": "Day after a party",
		"left": "Last night's pizza",
		"right": "Only water"
	},
	"dlm-23-en": {
		"id": "dlm-23-en",
		"prompt": "In front of a naked person",
		"left": "You stare at them",
		"right": "You stare at the ground",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-24-en": {
		"id": "dlm-24-en",
		"prompt": "Perfect excuse",
		"left": "Family problem",
		"right": "Health problem"
	},
	"dlm-25-en": {
		"id": "dlm-25-en",
		"prompt": "Sex slave to",
		"left": "Person to your left",
		"right": "Person to your right",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-26-en": {
		"id": "dlm-26-en",
		"prompt": "Fight against",
		"left": "A tiger",
		"right": "A shark"
	},
	"dlm-27-en": {
		"id": "dlm-27-en",
		"prompt": "Drive",
		"left": "The Batmobile",
		"right": "The Ghostbusters car"
	},
	"dlm-28-en": {
		"id": "dlm-28-en",
		"prompt": "Sexually attracted to",
		"left": "Door handles",
		"right": "Vacuums",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-29-en": {
		"id": "dlm-29-en",
		"prompt": "Your walk",
		"left": "Cowboy",
		"right": "Ballerina"
	},
	"dlm-30-en": {
		"id": "dlm-30-en",
		"prompt": "Shopping spree",
		"left": "With pleasure!",
		"right": "No, thank you..."
	},
	"dlm-31-en": {
		"id": "dlm-31-en",
		"prompt": "Subscription",
		"left": "Netflix",
		"right": "Disney+"
	},
	"dlm-32-en": {
		"id": "dlm-32-en",
		"prompt": "Night to yourself",
		"left": "1000 piece puzzle",
		"right": "1000 page novel"
	},
	"dlm-33-en": {
		"id": "dlm-33-en",
		"prompt": "At the store",
		"left": "You get 10 times more than you need",
		"right": "You forget half your list"
	},
	"dlm-34-en": {
		"id": "dlm-34-en",
		"prompt": "Two people fighting",
		"left": "You film them",
		"right": "You separate them"
	},
	"dlm-35-en": {
		"id": "dlm-35-en",
		"prompt": "Sneezing while drunk",
		"left": "You fart at the same time",
		"right": "You vomit in your mouth",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-36-en": {
		"id": "dlm-36-en",
		"prompt": "Your friend is being cheated on",
		"left": "You tell them",
		"right": "You keep the secret"
	},
	"dlm-37-en": {
		"id": "dlm-37-en",
		"prompt": "Masturbation",
		"left": "3 times per year",
		"right": "3 times per day",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-38-en": {
		"id": "dlm-38-en",
		"prompt": "Handcuffed for life to",
		"left": "A 10ft ladder",
		"right": "A goat"
	},
	"dlm-39-en": {
		"id": "dlm-39-en",
		"prompt": "Eat jam out of",
		"left": "Celebrity of choice's butthole",
		"right": "Gollum's mouth",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-40-en": {
		"id": "dlm-40-en",
		"prompt": "Your future",
		"left": "Dead in 10 years",
		"right": "Immortality"
	},
	"dlm-41-en": {
		"id": "dlm-41-en",
		"prompt": "Lick a body smeared with",
		"left": "Chocolate",
		"right": "Guacamole",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-42-en": {
		"id": "dlm-42-en",
		"prompt": "World Champion of",
		"left": "Rock, Paper, Scissors",
		"right": "Read light, green light"
	},
	"dlm-43-en": {
		"id": "dlm-43-en",
		"prompt": "Hit with a baseball bat",
		"left": "Wasp nest",
		"right": "Your neighbor"
	},
	"dlm-44-en": {
		"id": "dlm-44-en",
		"prompt": "Radio",
		"left": "Classic hits",
		"right": "Top 100"
	},
	"dlm-45-en": {
		"id": "dlm-45-en",
		"prompt": "In the street",
		"left": "Step in dog shit",
		"right": "Pigeon poops on you"
	},
	"dlm-46-en": {
		"id": "dlm-46-en",
		"prompt": "Vacation home",
		"left": "Vatican",
		"right": "Versailles"
	},
	"dlm-47-en": {
		"id": "dlm-47-en",
		"prompt": "Furniture",
		"left": "IKEA",
		"right": "Grandparents' antiques"
	},
	"dlm-48-en": {
		"id": "dlm-48-en",
		"prompt": "Conspiracy",
		"left": "First steps on the Moon",
		"right": "JFK's assassination"
	},
	"dlm-49-en": {
		"id": "dlm-49-en",
		"prompt": "Videogame",
		"left": "Mario Kart",
		"right": "Minecraft"
	},
	"dlm-50-en": {
		"id": "dlm-50-en",
		"prompt": "Seashore",
		"left": "Crowded sandy beach",
		"right": "Deserted pebble beach"
	},
	"dlm-51-en": {
		"id": "dlm-51-en",
		"prompt": "Take a dump",
		"left": "With someone in the next stall",
		"right": "While talking on the phone"
	},
	"dlm-52-en": {
		"id": "dlm-52-en",
		"prompt": "Free for life",
		"left": "Condoms",
		"right": "Carrots",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-53-en": {
		"id": "dlm-53-en",
		"prompt": "Speak like",
		"left": "Yoda",
		"right": "Darth Vader"
	},
	"dlm-54-en": {
		"id": "dlm-54-en",
		"prompt": "The hardest to find",
		"left": "The G spot",
		"right": "Waldo",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-55-en": {
		"id": "dlm-55-en",
		"prompt": "Computer",
		"left": "Apple",
		"right": "Windows"
	},
	"dlm-56-en": {
		"id": "dlm-56-en",
		"prompt": "In your bedroom",
		"left": "Mosquito",
		"right": "Baby"
	},
	"dlm-57-en": {
		"id": "dlm-57-en",
		"prompt": "Best friend",
		"left": "Weird Al",
		"right": "Dwayne \"The Rock\" Johnson"
	},
	"dlm-58-en": {
		"id": "dlm-58-en",
		"prompt": "Love life",
		"left": "Very complicated double life",
		"right": "Abstinence"
	},
	"dlm-59-en": {
		"id": "dlm-59-en",
		"prompt": "Ruins pizza",
		"left": "Anchovies",
		"right": "Olives"
	},
	"dlm-60-en": {
		"id": "dlm-60-en",
		"prompt": "In your coffee",
		"left": "Splash of milk",
		"right": "Splash of whiskey"
	},
	"dlm-61-en": {
		"id": "dlm-61-en",
		"prompt": "Cheated on",
		"left": "You forgive them... 2 years later",
		"right": "You set fire to their apartment"
	},
	"dlm-62-en": {
		"id": "dlm-62-en",
		"prompt": "Dare",
		"left": "Hook up with someone",
		"right": "Snort a chili pepper"
	},
	"dlm-63-en": {
		"id": "dlm-63-en",
		"prompt": "When you get a ticket",
		"left": "$50 and we forget it happened?",
		"right": "My taxes pay for your salary!"
	},
	"dlm-64-en": {
		"id": "dlm-64-en",
		"prompt": "Your dating pattern",
		"left": "Let's take it month by month",
		"right": "Till death do us part"
	},
	"dlm-65-en": {
		"id": "dlm-65-en",
		"prompt": "Fetich",
		"left": "Feet",
		"right": "Latex",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-66-en": {
		"id": "dlm-66-en",
		"prompt": "James Bond",
		"left": "Sean Connery",
		"right": "Daniel Craig"
	},
	"dlm-67-en": {
		"id": "dlm-67-en",
		"prompt": "To get a promotion",
		"left": "Loooooots of overtime",
		"right": "1 hour in bed with your boss",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-68-en": {
		"id": "dlm-68-en",
		"prompt": "Your skin covered in",
		"left": "Fur",
		"right": "Scales"
	},
	"dlm-69-en": {
		"id": "dlm-69-en",
		"prompt": "Your car",
		"left": "Optimus Prime",
		"right": "Lightning McQueen"
	},
	"dlm-70-en": {
		"id": "dlm-70-en",
		"prompt": "You at school",
		"left": "Hermione Granger",
		"right": "Bart Simpson"
	},
	"dlm-71-en": {
		"id": "dlm-71-en",
		"prompt": "Wearing clothes",
		"left": "Clean but damp",
		"right": "Dry but dirty"
	},
	"dlm-72-en": {
		"id": "dlm-72-en",
		"prompt": "Wake up to",
		"left": "The Star-spangled Banner",
		"right": "Repeating ding of a triangle"
	},
	"dlm-73-en": {
		"id": "dlm-73-en",
		"prompt": "Instant arousal",
		"left": "Aragorn",
		"right": "Legolas",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-74-en": {
		"id": "dlm-74-en",
		"prompt": "Date",
		"left": "A cop for their handcuffs",
		"right": "A jockey for their whip",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-75-en": {
		"id": "dlm-75-en",
		"prompt": "On TV",
		"left": "Reruns of Grey's Anatomy",
		"right": "Documentary about fly larvae"
	},
	"dlm-76-en": {
		"id": "dlm-76-en",
		"prompt": "When you're high",
		"left": "Build Legos",
		"right": "Watch Planet Earth",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-77-en": {
		"id": "dlm-77-en",
		"prompt": "Walk barefoot on",
		"left": "Legos",
		"right": "Moose droppings"
	},
	"dlm-78-en": {
		"id": "dlm-78-en",
		"prompt": "Find in your car",
		"left": "Use condom",
		"right": "Dead squirrel",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-79-en": {
		"id": "dlm-79-en",
		"prompt": "Breakup phrase",
		"left": "It's not you, it's me",
		"right": "Things were moving too quickly"
	},
	"dlm-80-en": {
		"id": "dlm-80-en",
		"prompt": "Infuriating in the check-out line",
		"left": "Cashier who chats with everyone",
		"right": "Geezer who counts all his coins"
	},
	"dlm-81-en": {
		"id": "dlm-81-en",
		"prompt": "Superpower for a day",
		"left": "Invisibility",
		"right": "Flight"
	},
	"dlm-82-en": {
		"id": "dlm-82-en",
		"prompt": "Roommates",
		"left": "A professional mime",
		"right": "A loud snorer"
	},
	"dlm-83-en": {
		"id": "dlm-83-en",
		"prompt": "Unlikely career",
		"left": "Circus clown",
		"right": "Shark trainer"
	},
	"dlm-84-en": {
		"id": "dlm-84-en",
		"prompt": "Stranded on a desert island",
		"left": "A lifetime supply of mayonnaise",
		"right": "A library of books in a language you don't understand"
	},
	"dlm-85-en": {
		"id": "dlm-85-en",
		"prompt": "Worst thing to find in your closet",
		"left": "A raccoon",
		"right": "A haunted doll"
	},
	"dlm-86-en": {
		"id": "dlm-86-en",
		"prompt": "First date activity",
		"left": "A competitive eating contest",
		"right": "An intense escape room"
	},
	"dlm-87-en": {
		"id": "dlm-87-en",
		"prompt": "Unwanted superpower",
		"left": "Every time you sneeze, you teleport randomly",
		"right": "Every time you blink, you switch languages"
	},
	"dlm-88-en": {
		"id": "dlm-88-en",
		"prompt": "Haunted experience",
		"left": "An endless loop of spooky whispers",
		"right": "A shadow that moves on its own"
	},
	"dlm-89-en": {
		"id": "dlm-89-en",
		"prompt": "Worst reality show to star in",
		"left": "Cooking with bugs",
		"right": "Living with your ex"
	},
	"dlm-90-en": {
		"id": "dlm-90-en",
		"prompt": "A strange law",
		"left": "Must wear a chicken costume every Tuesday",
		"right": "Can only eat soup with a fork"
	},
	"dlm-91-en": {
		"id": "dlm-91-en",
		"prompt": "Worst thing to lose for a week",
		"left": "Your voice",
		"right": "Your phone"
	},
	"dlm-92-en": {
		"id": "dlm-92-en",
		"prompt": "Unusual pet",
		"left": "A clingy octopus",
		"right": "A grumpy hedgehog"
	},
	"dlm-93-en": {
		"id": "dlm-93-en",
		"prompt": "Time travel dilemma",
		"left": "Stuck in the age of dinosaurs",
		"right": "Stuck in the distant future with no humans"
	},
	"dlm-94-en": {
		"id": "dlm-94-en",
		"prompt": "Embarrassing celebrity encounter",
		"left": "Spilling coffee on them",
		"right": "Tripping and falling into their arms"
	},
	"dlm-95-en": {
		"id": "dlm-95-en",
		"prompt": "You win a lifetime supply of",
		"left": "Cheese",
		"right": "Bubble wrap"
	},
	"dlm-96-en": {
		"id": "dlm-96-en",
		"prompt": "You can only listen to",
		"left": "The same song forever",
		"right": "A random playlist that changes every minute"
	},
	"dlm-97-en": {
		"id": "dlm-97-en",
		"prompt": "Weirdest good luck charm",
		"left": "A jar of toenails",
		"right": "A cursed teddy bear"
	},
	"dlm-98-en": {
		"id": "dlm-98-en",
		"prompt": "Pick a punishment",
		"left": "Sing every word you speak",
		"right": "Hop everywhere instead of walking"
	},
	"dlm-99-en": {
		"id": "dlm-99-en",
		"prompt": "Swap your nose with",
		"left": "An elephant's trunk",
		"right": "A butterfly's antennae"
	},
	"dlm-100-en": {
		"id": "dlm-100-en",
		"prompt": "Worst alarm clock sound",
		"left": "A baby crying",
		"right": "A drill sergeant screaming at you"
	},
	"dlm-101-en": {
		"id": "dlm-101-en",
		"prompt": "Strangest thing to find in your fridge",
		"left": "A live goldfish",
		"right": "A tiny gnome having a picnic"
	},
	"dlm-102-en": {
		"id": "dlm-102-en",
		"prompt": "Worst job offer",
		"left": "Professional armpit sniffer",
		"right": "Official sewage taste tester"
	},
	"dlm-103-en": {
		"id": "dlm-103-en",
		"prompt": "You wake up one morning and you are",
		"left": "Three feet tall",
		"right": "Ten feet tall"
	},
	"dlm-104-en": {
		"id": "dlm-104-en",
		"prompt": "Your new roommate is",
		"left": "A professional clown",
		"right": "An amateur magician"
	},
	"dlm-105-en": {
		"id": "dlm-105-en",
		"prompt": "Your laugh now sounds like",
		"left": "A donkey braying",
		"right": "A car alarm"
	},
	"dlm-106-en": {
		"id": "dlm-106-en",
		"prompt": "Unwanted transformation",
		"left": "You have lobster claws for hands",
		"right": "Your skin glows neon pink"
	},
	"dlm-107-en": {
		"id": "dlm-107-en",
		"prompt": "Every meal for a month is",
		"left": "Cold soup",
		"right": "Unseasoned boiled chicken"
	},
	"dlm-108-en": {
		"id": "dlm-108-en",
		"prompt": "New annoying superpower",
		"left": "You can read minds but only when people are thinking about food",
		"right": "You can teleport but only to the nearest gas station"
	},
	"dlm-109-en": {
		"id": "dlm-109-en",
		"prompt": "Haunted by",
		"left": "A friendly but overly chatty ghost",
		"right": "A spooky but silent shadow figure"
	},
	"dlm-110-en": {
		"id": "dlm-110-en",
		"prompt": "Worst fashion trend to follow",
		"left": "Clothes made entirely of duct tape",
		"right": "Shoes made of bread"
	},
	"dlm-111-en": {
		"id": "dlm-111-en",
		"prompt": "Every time you sneeze",
		"left": "You switch bodies with the nearest person",
		"right": "You teleport to a random location within 50 miles"
	},
	"dlm-112-en": {
		"id": "dlm-112-en",
		"prompt": "Your internet history is shown to",
		"left": "Your boss",
		"right": "Your parents"
	},
	"dlm-113-en": {
		"id": "dlm-113-en",
		"prompt": "Live inside a world where everyone communicates only by",
		"left": "Song",
		"right": "Mime"
	},
	"dlm-114-en": {
		"id": "dlm-114-en",
		"prompt": "Your shadow suddenly",
		"left": "Starts talking to you",
		"right": "Moves on its own"
	},
	"dlm-115-en": {
		"id": "dlm-115-en",
		"prompt": "You can only eat with",
		"left": "Chopsticks for everything",
		"right": "A single spoon for every meal"
	},
	"dlm-116-en": {
		"id": "dlm-116-en",
		"prompt": "A tattoo magically appears on your forehead saying",
		"left": "\"I love pineapples on pizza\"",
		"right": "\"Ask me about my ex\""
	},
	"dlm-117-en": {
		"id": "dlm-117-en",
		"prompt": "You have to wear",
		"left": "A swimsuit to a formal event",
		"right": "A tuxedo to the beach"
	},
	"dlm-118-en": {
		"id": "dlm-118-en",
		"prompt": "Your alarm clock is now",
		"left": "A rooster that lives in your bedroom",
		"right": "A random stranger who yells at you every morning"
	},
	"dlm-119-en": {
		"id": "dlm-119-en",
		"prompt": "Your phone autocorrects every text to",
		"left": "Shakespearean English",
		"right": "Pirate slang"
	},
	"dlm-120-en": {
		"id": "dlm-120-en",
		"prompt": "Your sneeze sounds like",
		"left": "A trumpet blast",
		"right": "A high-pitched scream"
	},
	"dlm-121-en": {
		"id": "dlm-121-en",
		"prompt": "You can only watch adult films with",
		"left": "Your parents in the room",
		"right": "A group of complete strangers",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-122-en": {
		"id": "dlm-122-en",
		"prompt": "Your next date involves",
		"left": "Playing with food",
		"right": "Testing sex toys",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-123-en": {
		"id": "dlm-123-en",
		"prompt": "You're magically forced to shout during sex",
		"left": "\"Take me to the moon!\"",
		"right": "\"I'm the king/queen of the jungle!\"",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-124-en": {
		"id": "dlm-124-en",
		"prompt": "You must walk down the street wearing",
		"left": "A sexy nurse costume",
		"right": "Leather underwear",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-125-en": {
		"id": "dlm-125-en",
		"prompt": "You must accidentally send a spicy text to",
		"left": "Your boss",
		"right": "Your former teacher",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-126-en": {
		"id": "dlm-126-en",
		"prompt": "You find out your neighbor is",
		"left": "A professional stripper",
		"right": "A director of adult films",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-127-en": {
		"id": "dlm-127-en",
		"prompt": "You're hypnotized to feel pleasure every time",
		"left": "Someone says 'thank you'",
		"right": "You hear a doorbell",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-128-en": {
		"id": "dlm-128-en",
		"prompt": "Your partner can only get in the mood if you're dressed as",
		"left": "A cartoon character",
		"right": "A ridiculous superhero",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-129-en": {
		"id": "dlm-129-en",
		"prompt": "You can only have intimate moments in",
		"left": "A crowded elevator",
		"right": "A very quiet library",
		"nsfw": true
	},
	"dlm-130-en": {
		"id": "dlm-130-en",
		"prompt": "Your NSFW superpower is",
		"left": "You can attract anyone with a wink",
		"right": "You become irresistible when covered in glitter",
		"nsfw": true
	}
}
